what's up everyone tammy's only 5 foot
with a very special video today
so I was sitting at home like I usually
do watching soccer around
and I was watching sucker on episode six
moba dune
for those who don't know that is the
episode that folks on song mac and
Sonia's birthday
and and I thought to myself we suck
on fans we all play games
on our birthday that involves sock on
theme
so I thought I would show some of you
non-stock on fans
what kind of games we play I'm so I'm
going to go through a ton
of games that maybe you'll want to do
for maybe your birthday maybe like
help like if your kids want to have a
soccer themed party
maybe this will give you some pointers i
don't give a
so the first game is a game called
match the characters where everyone this
is a
this is kind of a party game everyone
get all of the kids all like the
for three four years I don't
care tell them to draw soccer and
characters
and draw each character two times two
songs
two Manics do barbies and when you do
get all of the cows like this put them
all
face down I'm sure you can all see
what's going on here
but after all the cards i'll place down
get all the little and tell
themselves
flipping over cows until they match two
characters like
off of a worm that's Manic holding a
shotgun
i'll flip over this one oh I did not win
but that's
his bro Sonic so i'll flip those over
and then they will bring you bring over
like another key get on
get like a little tv from down the
street don't you flip all the cards
you'll flip over
like a cow like that boom you got queen
alina holding
a basketball and then
boom you got Sonia so again timmy's a
failure and
so and then of course you'll get the
true soccer fact
like me might not want to let us play
any games or this is going to happen
we'll get
boom we'll get two Gods got Bobby
got another Bobby now what's special
about this game is Bobby is like
exotic of the forbidden one but like the
Sonic on version it was like Bobby the
rich one
and if you flip over Bobby you
automatically win the game
game's on little timmy lost and
the hell even the birthday boy loses if
he doesn't get Bobby
that's that's pretty much the first game
as you can see i'll flip them i'll show
you the other cards you got
you got Mindy with big ass
big ass tits got two minis with
tits that
that's quadruple tits right there that's
what I like to see
that's what daddy I see so now we are
going to move on
to the second game which I like to call
put the doll bill in Bobby's pocket
this is the game I would always play i
would always ask my parents to do this
one because
i like it and the birthday boy gets a
little something
special if you know what I mean
now what I mean by that is all of the
little kids that showed by the birthday
party
tell them to get their their getting
their momma's watch get like a doll
because
you're gonna play a little game put the
dollar bill in Bobby spock it's a lot
like pin to tell the donkey
you step back if you have some friends
spin you around
i didn't have any friends growing up so
i'll just play by myself
and just close your eyes and
you just put it forward try to get as
close as you can
to Bobby's pocket and then when you do
all of the dollar bills are gathered up
and given to the birthday boy that way
even the kids
who forgot to bring presents because as
i just said kids
my birthday parties and my parents will
always put money on before me
that way the little boy who has his
birthday
can even goals too they can do this i
don't give a
and when they get like all the money
all the money goes to the birthday boy
so I hope you enjoyed all these power
i'll be looking forward to
hopefully be invited I mean nobody
invited me to birthday parties when i
was growing up
i mean